Hu Shuhan 胡舒涵

245, Section 5, Roosevelt Road, Wenshan District, Taipei City 116, Taiwan

☐ +886 910-384-478 · ► 1119han@gmail.com · ○ github.com/RocketSH

Objective: Fullstack Developer

Four years in footwear manufacturing made me understand that although automation techniques are already commonly implemented on the factory floor, there are still many repetitive, everyday tasks in office work that remain to be optimized. Therefore I have decided to learn software development to be able to automate dayto-day tasks and save time and money, both for my clients and for myself.

I have recently graduated from a three-month bootcamp organized by 5xRuby, a Taiwan-based software development company specializing in Ruby on Rails. During the course, I have learned the basics of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails, and Git version control, also self-learned PostgreSQL, JavaScript.

Profolio

Personal Blog @ rocketgirl.io

ReactJS, HTML, CSS, GatsbyJS

Email Newsletter Website ₹ goodbyt.es

[Frontend] HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, SortableJS, AJAX Stimulus

[Backend] Ruby on Rails

[Ruby Gem] Devise, Nokogiri, Carrierwave, AWS S3

[Database] PostgreSQL

[Email Service Provider] Mailgun



Work Experience

Pouchen Group

Frontend Developer, iNet

• Coordinate with technical lead, internal developers, customers on current project [HTML, CSS, Vue CLI]

Jul 2015-Oct 2019

Taichung, Taiwan Jun 2019-Oct 2019

Taipei, Taiwan Jul 2020-

SAP CO of Data Conversion Specialist, Pouchen Group

- · Assisted the migration of footwear-related data from a legacy ERP system within six-month
- Set up data transformation logic, testing and debugging of data extraction procedures, analyzing error logs

Footwear Costing Supervisor, Pouchen Group

- · Cooperated with the brand leadership of Salomon, Arc'teryx, Mavic, and Wilson, as well as the Development and Merchandising departments in order to optimize costs based on the target FOB
- · Assisted subordinate ten Taiwanese and Vietnamese team members with Cost Breakdown analysis

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam May 2017-Jun 2019

Footwear Costing Specialist, Pouchen Group

Dongguan, China Jul 2015–May 2017

- Collecting raw material price and negotiating product specifics with Tier Two suppliers twice a year
- Collecting and analyzing product-related tasks assigned by the Product Manager and Costing Manager twice a year for business negotiation with client

Credit Card Specialist, Citibank

• Application verification

Taipei, Taiwan Jul 2013–Nov 2014

Education

Astro Camp Ruby on Rails Bootcamp, 5xRuby

Ruby, Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, and ES6

Taipei, Taiwan March–June 2020

National Dong Hwa University, College of Management

Bachelor of Arts — Double Major in Economics and Business Administration in Finance

Hualien, Taiwan Graduated June 2013

Other Skills

- Chinese (Mandarin) Native Language, English Fluent (TOEIC 840), Vietnamese — Basic (A2)
- Microsoft Excel PivotTable report, Google Docs, iWork